A Finding Aid to the Fischbach Gallery Records, 1937-2015, bulk 1963-1977, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fiscgall
Archives of American Art
- Artists and Exhibitions Files, 1937-1977; Series 1; (Boxes 1-18, 28; 18 linear feet)
  - Wurmfeld, Sanford (Box 18)
    - Photos of Works of Art, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Negatives and Transparencies of Works of Art, circa 1969 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "According to the Letter" (Box 18)
    - Artists' Biographical Information, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Printed Materials, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "American Indian Rugs" (Box 18)
    - Photos of Installations, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - "Direct Representation" (Box 18)
    - General Information, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Printed Material, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Photos of Installations, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Photos and Negatives of Works of Art, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "Eccentric Abstraction" (Box 18)
    - Printed Materials, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1966 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Photos of Installations, circa 1966 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1966 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "18th and 19th Century Miniatures from the Royal Courts, India" (Box 18)
    - Exhibition Announcement, circa 1960s (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "Games Without Rules" (Box 18)
    - Printed Materials, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - "Hard Center" (Box 18)
    - Artists' Biographical Information, circa 1963 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Printed Materials, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Photos of Works of Art, circa 1963 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - "Six Women" (Box 18)
    - Exhibition Announcement, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Photos of Installations, circa 1960s (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1960s (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Photo of Works of Art by Jack Lenk, (Oversized Material from Box 12, F10) (Box 28)
  - Exhibition Catalog from Robert Ryman, (Oversized Material from Box 15, F40-41) (Box 28)
- General Gallery Correspondence, 1962-1974; Series 2; (Box 18-19; 1.75 linear feet)
  General Gallery Correspondence consists of correspondence between Fischbach and other galleries, museums, and clients. Generally, the correspondence concerns client development, loans, consignments, exhibitions, framing, transportation, and a variety of topics. The many museums and galleries with which Fischbach Gallery corresponded includes the Corcoran Gallery of Art, the Museum of Modern Art, the New Gallery, San Francisco Museum of Art, and the Whitney Museum, along with many colleges and university art galleries and museums. Correspondence is in alphabetical order by name business, company, museum, organization, or person.
  - General Correspondence, 1965-1970; (7 folders) (Box 18, Folder 38-45)
  - Correspondence, A-I, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, J-Z, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence with New Artists, 1968-1970; (3 folders) (Box 18, Folder 48-50)
  - Correspondence with Non-Gallery Artists, 1965-1970 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous Consignment and Loan Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence Regarding Loans, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence Regarding Loans, 1969-1972; (4 folders) (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, General, 1962-1974; (6 folders) (Box 19, Folder 5-10)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, A, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, B, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, c, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, D, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, E, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, F, 1971, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, G-H, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, I-K, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, L-M, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, N-R, 1971-1974; (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, S-U, 1969-1974; (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
  - Museum and Gallery Correspondence, V-Z, 1971-1974; (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 24-25)
  - Acme Van and Storage, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Call For Help, INC. Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Daytons Gallery 12, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Daytons Gallery 12, Gallery Ricke, Galerie Ileana Sonnabend, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Morris and Walsh and Eston Color Craft, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Business Records, 1969-1971; Series 3; (Box 27; 0.3 linear feet)
  Business records consist of an address book, materials regarding the production of art posters, gallery floor plans, schedules of exhibitions shown at the Fischbach Gallery, guest lists, mailing lists, and a roster of Fischbach artists among other scattered records.
  - Address Book, circa 1970; (2 folders) (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
  - Concerning Art Posters, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Gallery Plans, circa 1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Gallery Schedules, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Guest Lists, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lists of Works of Art, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Mailing Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Notebook, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Press Lists, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Roster of Artists, circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Financial Records, 1963-1975; Series 4; (Boxes 20-25; 4.5 linear feet)
  Financial records document sales, payments, and loans between the Gallery, buyers, and artists. Many of the artists are also represented in the Artists and Exhibition Files series. Additional financial records document framing, transportation and delivery, publicity, insurance, and other routine gallery business. General financial records which include bank statements, ledgers, insurance, and travel accounts.
  This series is arranged as 3 subseries
  4.1: Artists Financial Records, 1963-1975 (Box 20-21)
  4.2: Alphabetical Financial Records, 1963-1974, (Box 21-25)
  4.3: General Financial Records, 1967-1973 (Box 25)
  - Artists' Financial Records, 1963-1975; 4.1
    - Antonakos, Stephen, 1966-1973; (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Arnold, Anne, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Assetto, Frank, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Baer, Jo, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Baynard, Ed, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bechtle, Robert, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Bennett, John, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bishop, James, 1966-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bladen, Ronald, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Bosson, Jack, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Brecht, George, 1965-1970 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Carswell, John, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Chamberlain, Wynn, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - D'Arcangelo, Allan, 1963-1970; (6 folders) (Box 20, Folder 15-20)
    - Daniel, Mell, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Gene, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Drummond, Sally, 1967-1972 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Dunn, Anne, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Ferro, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Frazier, Paul, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Gianakos, Stylianos, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Gilardi, Piero, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Gorchov, Ron, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Grosvenor, Robert, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Haber, Ira Joel, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Harm, Elizabeth, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Hesse, Eva, 1967-1975; (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 33-34)
    - Hokanson, Hans, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Insley, Will, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Jaquette, Yvonne, 1971-1976 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Jenkins, Paul, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Jensen, Bill, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Katz, Alex, 1962-1973; (5 folders) (Box 20, Folder 40-44)
    - Kilstrom, Kenneth, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Kogelnik, Kiki, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Krushenick, Nicholas, 1965-1969 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Kuehn, Gary, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Kulicke, 1965-1969 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Kuriloff, Aaron, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Laganne, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Lenk, Thomas, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Levine, Les, 1965-1970; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Loving, Al, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Mangold, Robert, 1964-1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Mangold, Sylvia, 1969-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Knox, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Marzollo, Claudio, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Mathieu, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Morris, Robert, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Moss, Joe, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Noland, Kenneth, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Ohlson, Doug, 1964-1972; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Parker, Ray, 1970-1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Pavlos, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Pfahler, Georg Karl, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Ryan, Anne, 1968-1970; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
    - Ryman, Robert, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
    - Schneeman, George, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Shostak, Ed, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Slavin, Arlene, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Tony, 1967-1971; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 26-27)
    - Stavrinos, George, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Stefanelli, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Steiner, Michael, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Stella, Frank, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Sugarman, George, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Swain, Robert, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Tadasky, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Tomarelli (?), Andrew, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Viner, Frank Lincoln, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Wurmfeld, Sanford, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Yascoe, Donald, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Multiple Artists, 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Alphabetical Financial Records, 1963-1974; 4.2
    - A, 1963-1973; (10 folders) (Box 21, Folder 41-50)
    - A.P.F., 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 51-52)
    - Accurate Messenger Service, 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 53-54)
    - Acme Van Company, 1968-1972; (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 55-56)
    - Alcon Picture Framers Co., 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Art Delivery Service, 1964-1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - The Art Gallery, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Art News, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - B, 1964-1966; (5 folders) (Box 22, Folder 5-9)
    - Berkely Express, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Bienalle of Art, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Burckhardt, Rudolph, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - C, 1964-1970; (4 folders) (Box 22, Folder 13-16)
    - D, 1964-1970; (4 folders) (Box 22, Folder 17-20)
    - Dain/Schiff, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Delmore and A-1, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - E, 1966-1974; (4 folders) (Box 22, Folder 23-26)
    - F, 1963-1974; (5 folders) (Box 22, Folder 27-31)
    - G, 1964-1974; (5 folders) (Box 22, Folder 32-36)
    - H, 1964-1974 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - H, 1964-1974; (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
    - Halvorse Art Express, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Hanks Transportation Service, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Herald Tribune, 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Herbert Charles and Co., 1963-1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Hudson Shipping Co., Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - I, 1964-1974; (3 folders) (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
    - J, 1963-1974; (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 13-16)
    - K, 1963-1974; (5 folders) (Box 23, Folder 17-21)
    - Kulicke Frames Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - L, 1963-1974; (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 23-26)
    - M, 1962-1974; (5 folders) (Box 23, Folder 27-32)
    - M, 1961-1974; (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 33-36)
    - O, 1964-1974; (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - O, 1964-1974; (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - O, 1963-1974; (4 folders) (Box 24, Folder 3-6)
    - "Petty Cash", circa 1960s-1970s; (4 folders) (Box 24, Folder 7-10)
    - Q, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - R, 1964-1974; (3 folders) (Box 24, Folder 12-14)
    - S, 1962-1974; (7 folders) (Box 24, Folder 13-19)
    - T, 1964-1974; (3 folders) (Box 24, Folder 20-22)
    - Travel, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - U, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - V, 1963-1974; (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 25-26)
    - W-Z, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 27-29)
    - W.R. Keating and Co., 1964-1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - General Financial Records, 1967-1973; 4.3
    - Accounts Receivable Schedule, 1967-1970; (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - Bank Information, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Bank Check Records, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Miscellaneous, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Ledger--Sales, Receipts, Purchases, Disbursements, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Settled Claims, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Travel Accounts, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Printed Material, 1963-1972; Series 5; (Box 26: 6 folders)
  This small series consists of miscellaneous business cards, clippings, non-Fischbach exhibition announcements, and a guide to New York art galleries by Ron Williams dated 1972.
  - Business Cards, circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Clippings Concerning Fischbach Gallery, 1965-1969 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Office Catalogs, 1963-1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Ron Williams--"An Artist's Guide to Some New York Galleries,", 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified, circa 1970s (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Photographs, circa 1960s; Series 6; (Box 26: 2 folders)
  Photographs include several photos from the Thiabaut Gallery and unidentified photographs of landscapes.
  - Photos from Thiabaut Gallery, circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photos of Landscapes, circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Addition to the Fischbach Gallery Records, circa 1960s-2015; Series 7; 14 Linear feet Box 29-42
  Addition to the Fischbach Gallery records dates from circa 1960s-2015 and consists of inventory and client sales records in the form of card indexes.
  The series is arranged as two subseries
  7.1: Inventory Card Indexes, circa 1960s-2015 (12.1 linear feet; Box 29-41)
  7.2: Client Sales Card Index, circa 1970s-2000s (1.9 linear feet; Box 41-42)
  - Inventory Card Indexes, circa 1960s-2015; 7.1; 12.1 Linear feet Box 29-41
    Inventory card indexes date from circa 1960s-2015 and contain index cards used to keep track of the inventory and sales of works of art. Organized by artist, index cards include fields for title, dimension, medium, date, price, place of signature, provenance, owner, and purchaser of the work. Not all fields are complete for each index card. In some instances, a representation of the work as either a print-out or photograph is stapled to the back of the card. Supplemental notes are also attached in some instances, and include additional client information, correspondence, shipping and consignment receipts, business cards, and additional provenance information.
    The subseries is arranged as two sub-subseries to reflect two distinct sets of alphabetical A-Z card indexes maintained by the gallery.
    7.1.1: First A-Z Sequence, circa 1960s-2015 (4.8 linear feet; Box 29-33)
    7.1.2: Second A-Z Sequence, circa 1960s-2015 (7.3 linear feet; Box 33-41)
    - First A-Z Sequence, circa 1960s-2015; 7.1.1; 4.8 Linear feet Box 29-33
      - Anderson, Neil, circa 1976-circa 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Arnold, Anne, circa 1964-circa1988 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
      - Avedisian, Edward, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Barr, Victoria, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Bechtle, Robert, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Bennett, John, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Bigbee, Brett, circa 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Bishop, James, 1966-1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Bladen, Ronald, circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Blaine, Nell, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 29, Folder 11-15)
      - Brainard, Joe, circa 1970s; circa 2007 (Box 29, Folder 16-18)
      - Brandt, Warren, 1975-1998 (Box 29, Folder 19-21)
      - Brazil, Rick, circa 1984 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Brecht, George, 1964-1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Button, John, 1975-1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - B, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Cady, Arthur, circa 1978-circa 1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Caranicas, Paul, 1978-1982 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Carsman, Jon, 1975-1982 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Cava, Anthony, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Clark, Emery, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Crile, Susan, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - C, Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - D'Arcangelo, Allan, circa 1960s-1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Dash, Robert, circa 1970s (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - David, Gene, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
      - De Kooning, Elaine, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Dewey, David, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Dodd, Lois, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 17-18)
      - Drummond, Sally, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Dugmore, Edward, circa 1968 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Dunn, Anne, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Durham, Brad, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Eisenman, Michael, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Erlebacher, Martha Mayer, 1992-1997 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Evans, Donald, circa 1970s (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Fiore, Joseph, circa 1975-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Frazier, Paul, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Freilicher, Jane, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 3-7)
      - Keiser, Doug, circa 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Kraft, Polly, circa 1980s-2014 (Box 31, Folder 9-13)
      - Laub, John, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
      - Loeb, David, 2002-2005 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Loftus, Peter, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 32, Folder 2-5)
      - Marshall, Brad, 2000-2014 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
      - Mazzucca, Anita, 2003-2014 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Mickilowski, Denise, 1999-2014 (Box 32, Folder 9-14)
      - Murphy, Catherine, circa 1977 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Parness, Charles, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Peyton, Gaines, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Pines, Suzanne, 1988-2003 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Rickert, Paul, 1991-2011 (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
      - Siejka, George, 2007-2008 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Simon, Leslie Horan, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Tapley, Emma, 1999-2014 (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
      - Tolstedt, Lowell, 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Tyng, Alexandra, 1995-2015 (Box 33, Folder 12-14)
      - Vaughn, Jeffrey, 2010-2013 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Winn, James, 2011-2013 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Second A-Z Sequence, circa 1960s-2015; 7.1.2; 7.3 Linear feet Box 33-41
      - Arnold, Anne, 1986; 1992 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Arzt, Tim, 1998-2005 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Avery, Milton, 2012-2014 (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
      - Behnke, Leigh, 1978-2013 (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
      - Berggruen, Helen, 1993-2013 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
      - Brainard, Joe, circa 1970s; circa 2000s (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Alice Dalton, 1986-2013 (Box 34, Folder 7-13)
      - Brown, Colin, 2004-2012 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Brown, Colin, 2004-2012 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
      - Bush, Jack, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Cobourn, Ryan, 2008-2012 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Cordell, Thomas, 1996-2011 (Box 35, Folder 5-7)
      - Craddock, Daisy, 2004-2014 (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
      - Davis, Gene, circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Dixon, Willard, circa 1980s-2007 (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
      - Drewa, Barbara Dixon, 1985-2014 (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
      - Evans, Christopher, 2007-2015 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Falato, John, 2005-2012 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Ferrandini, Robert, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Forrester, Patricia Tobacco, 1984-1992 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Foster, Fredericka, 2002-2013 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Frank, Kevin, 2014-2015 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Freilicher, Jane, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Fukushima, Michiyo, 2006-2008 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - F, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Garrigan, Kim, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Gerlach, Christopher, circa 1980s-1990 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Gianakos, Stylianos, circa 1968 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Gilardi, Piero, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Gitman, Victoria, 2002-2005 (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
      - Gola, Jeff, 2013-2015 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Goldstein, Daniel J., 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Gorchov, Ron, circa 1970s (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Gordon, Harvey, 1983-1990 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Gordon, Patrick S. (P.S.), 2007-2013; 1980-1990 (Box 36, Folder 18-20)
      - Grimes, Margaret, 1982-1986 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Grooms, Red, circa 1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Grosser, Maurice, circa 1978-1987 (Box 36, Folder 23-24)
      - Grosvenor, Robert, circa 1960s; 1986 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Gundelfinger, John, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Gunderson, Karen, 1982-1986 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - G, Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Haber, Ira Joel, 1969-1974 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Hagin, Nancy, 1980-2015 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Hagin, Nancy, 1980-2015 (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
      - Hansen, Glen, 1992-2014 (Box 37, Folder 6-11)
      - Harms, Elizabeth, 1972-1975 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Hendricks, David, 1984-1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Herman, Rose, 1981-1989 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Hesse, Eva, 1966-1970 (Box 37, Folder 15-16)
      - Holland, Glen, 1996-2008 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Holland, Glen, 1996-2008 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      - Hornak, Ian, 1977-1981 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Horton, Rick, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Imamura, Haruto Robert, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Insley, Will, 1966-1976 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Isham, Sheila, circa 1972 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Jacquette, Yvonne, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Jans, Candace, 1981-2014 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
      - Jensen, William, 1972-1975 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Jermann, David, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Joel, David, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Katz, Alex, 2012; 1965-1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Keiser, Duane, 1997-2001 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Kelley, John, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Kepets, Hugh, circa 1975-circa 1985 (Box 38, Folder 17-18)
      - Kilstrom, Kenneth, circa 1966-1968 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - King, Kevin, 1994-2003 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Krushenick, Nicholas, circa 1960s (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Kuehn, Gary, 1969-1972 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - K, Miscellaneous, 1966; 1983 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Lander, John, circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Lang, Daniel, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - L, Miscellaneous, circa 1960s (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Magalhães, Aloisio, circa 1978 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Mahaffey, Merrill, 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Mangold, Robert, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Mangold, Sylvia, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 30)